Sami Rivera Returns home and talks about the
Sami Rivera Vuelve a casa y habla del
Hey received for the evening and about Marina
Hey recibido por la velada y por Marina
Beijing betrayed by some
Beijing traicionada por algunos
content creators and nominated for a
creadores de contenido y nominada a un
beauty award in the United States
premio de belleza en Estados Unidos
streamer worried about
streamer preocupado por la salud mental
Comanche's mental health after the funa she experienced yesterday
de Comanche tras la funa que vivió ayer
Javier Oliveira firmly wins a lawsuit
Javier oliveira gana en firme un juicio
against a friend of Yiyo Juan Jerry mua
a un amigo de Yiyo Juan Jerry mua se
breaks down worried about her
rompe preocupada por su página de
Facebook page Avi and Luna complain about
Facebook Avi y Luna se quejan de los
wankers on the internet also Luna
pajeros en internet además también luna
complains that they have speculated a
se queja de que han especulado una
false news about her having a
noticia en falsa sobre ella de un
fling with a soccer player Germán
rollete con un futbolista Germán
Garmendia turns his back on Koku after
Garmendia da la espalda a koku después
the evening Willyrex and Vegeta in a
de la velada Willyrex y Vegeta en una
Dead series Gonsabela was invited to
serie del Dead gonsabela fue invitada a
the evening 3 by Goku himself Ricky
la velada 3 por el mismísimo Goku Ricky
canceled and his girlfriend defends him and
cancelado y su novia le defiende y
Spring speaks out about Kick all this
Spring se pronuncia sobre Kick todo esto
and much more here on your favorite gossip channel
y mucho más aquí en tu canal de chismes
family What's up my kids
favorito familia Qué pasa mi chavalería
How are you thank you And a thousand thanks for the
Cómo estáis gracias Y mil gracias por el
support you are giving to this channel
apoyo que le estáis dando a este canal
Yes, I have to remind you not to let your
Eso sí os tengo que recordar que no
guard down and that if  do you want
bajemos la guardia y que si queréis que
this type of content to continue I
siga siendo este tipo de contenido
need your support I
necesito vuestro apoyo necesito de
absolutely need you to press
manera obligatoria que pulses ahora
the Like button right now if you're watching
mismo el botón de Like si estás viendo
this video because remember if you don't
Este vídeo porque recuerda que si no le
press the like button the video will not be
das al botón de like el vídeo no se ve
in high quality it looks very bad also I
en alta calidad se ve muy mal además te
will be giving you a video game in each
estaré regalando un videojuego en cada
video at any point in the video
vídeo en cualquier momento del vídeo
you will see a code appear that you can
verás aparecer un código que puedes
redeem for a video game And if today it's
canjear por un videojuego Y si hoy ha
too late It's okay
llegado demasiado tarde No pasa nada
subscribe by activating the bell and
suscríbete activando la campanita y
try to be the first to enter every
Procura ser el primero en entrar cada
day every time I upload a video every
día cada vez que suba un vídeo todos los
day I upload videos more or less at the same
días subo vídeo más o menos a la misma
time and now let's leave the plate
hora y ahora sí vamos a dejar la chapa
grab some pipita and go to Lyon the
cogeros unas pipita y vamos al Lyon la
Mexican Rivers has returned home and
mexicana rivers ha vuelto a su casa y
today from her Setup she started live
hoy desde su Setup ha iniciado directo
trying to comment a little more or
intentando comentar un poquito más o
less on everything she's experienced in the last few days
menos todo lo vivido en los últimos días
at the beginning she commented that she had like some
al principio comenta que tenía como unas
certain notes of everything she
ciertas anotaciones de todo lo que
wanted to comment on but finally she
quería comentar pero que finalmente ha
decided to put herself in front of the camera and
decidido ponerse delante de la cámara y
let out what has to come out now
que salga lo que tenga que salir ahora
with what stupid stupidity are you going to come out I
con qué pendeja pendejada me vas a salir
was going to notice what I was going to say today
iba a notar lo que iba a decir hoy
write down and  It's going to be a list with points
anotar y va a ser una lista con puntos
that I wanted to touch on important things and
que quería tocar con cosas importantes y
I said you know what That's not me, I don't
dije sabes qué Esa no soy yo yo no
work like that, I always try to be
funciono así yo siempre intento ser
genuine with you guys, as I always am And
genuina con ustedes como soy siempre Y
that's what I'm going to do, that's what I'm going to
eso es lo que voy a hacer es lo que voy
do and because remember that apart from that,
a hacer y porque acuérdense que aparte
I'm very stupid and after
yo soy muy pendeja y después de estar
training for four months Boxing that I'm even more
entrenando cuatro meses Box que dé más
stupid from so much [ __ ] my head that they
pendeja de tanto chingazo la cabeza que
gave me in streams, I'm going to tell what I did during
me dieron streams cuento lo que hice en
the day but I think there are more
el día pero creo que cosas más
important things to tell than what I did
importantes que contar que hice el
today because apart from that, the only thing I
[__] día de hoy porque aparte lo único
did was fly from Spain, from Madrid to
que hice fue volar de España de Madrid
Monterrey The truth is that
hacia hacia Monterrey La verdad es que
at the moment that I'm recording
en estos momentos que estoy grabando
This video is still live and it hasn't
Este vídeo Todavía está en directo y no
finished starting to talk about
ha terminado de arrancar de hablar de
everything, so surely tomorrow I'll
todo por lo que seguramente mañana os
inform you much more and in the live shows I'll
informaré mucho más y en los directos
also be putting some
también os estaré poniendo alguna que
other things one of the things that he has
otra cosilla una de las cositas que ha
mentioned is for example how he convinced
comentado es por ejemplo como convenció
ibai to let him fight in a
a ibai de que le dejara pelear en un
second fight, decisions saying
segundo combate decisiones diciendo
[ __ ] his mother, I mean when I'm
chingue su madre o sea cuando estoy
between one thing and another I say eh his mother and I
entre una cosa y otra digo eh su madre y
do it, I don't think much no  I'm a
lo hago no pienso mucho no soy una
person who thinks a lot, I am governed by
persona que piense mucho yo me rijo por
the [ __ ] his mother and that's how I make all my
el chingue su madre y así tomo todas mis
decisions. Where do I start,
decisiones este por dónde empezar
tell me where do I start? No, I have no
díganme por dónde empiezo No no tengo
idea how to do this, nobody taught me, I've been
idea de cómo hacer esto nadie me enseñó
here for a short time, where the hell do I
llevo poquito tiempo aquí por donde
start? I've lived through a lot of things,
chucha empiezo viví muchísimas cosas
but I think what I'm going to do today is talk about
pero creo que lo que toca hoy es lo de
the fights, the evening and everything, everything that
las peleas la velada y todo todo que
has to do with that, and tomorrow,
tiene que ver con eso y ya mañana ya
tomorrow it's time to talk about the whole trip. Oh,
mañana tocará platicar de todo el viaje
thank you for being here these
eh agradecerles por estar aquí estos
last few days, it's been interesting,
últimos días ha estado curioso ha estado
everything has been interesting. But thank you for being here,
curioso todo Pero gracias por estar aquí
thank you for, I've seen all this
gracias por por he visto todo este
time, messages, messages of all kinds,
tiempo mensajes mensajes de todo tipo
right? Because that's what matters, that's what matters, what's
verdad porque es lo que importa es lo
left at the end of the day, sometimes it's difficult, it's
día queda que a veces es difícil es
also difficult to see that. Really. But
difícil además ver eso De verdad Pero
anyway, I'm going to stick with the
pues ni modo yo me voy a quedar con las
good things and the beautiful things, and that's what I'm
cosas buenas y las cosas bonitas y es lo
going to tell you, I'm telling you, I've seen
que les voy a contar les digo he visto
everything, but what I'm going to keep is
de todo pero lo que yo me quedo es con
the affection and the love that the people have given me,
el cariño y el amor que me ha dado la
you know, you know, I think you've
ustedes saben ustedes saben yo creo que
seen it and it's a lot, it's too much, it's
lo han visto y es es mucho es demasiado
really, I know them.  I also really appreciate that you
es es de verdad se los agradezco mucho
took the time to come
también Se tomaron el tiempo de venir
here whether it's to listen I have to say or to give me
aquí ya sea escuchar tengo que decir o
a boost all my mother well welcome I appreciate it I charge the same for the ads So no problem welcome don't worry let's focus on the negative things the difference is that some people have bad opinions I have received a lot but well that's not the important thing that's not important and I didn't focus on that I
importante y no me enfocar en eso me
focused on the good and I said mute yourself a
enfocar en lo bueno y le digo mutéate
little mute yourself and he says mute yourself let's see
tantito muteate y me dice se mutea ver
what happened And I told him you have to fight
qué pasó Y le dije tienes que peleé dos
twice he stays quiet for like a
veces se queda callado como por unos
good five seconds feet he hangs up on me
buenos cinco segundos pies me cuelga
this is incredible and live he says
esto es increíble y en directo él dice
something like he told them what he told me I do
algo como si les dijera lo que me dijo
n't know what I don't know what And I answered at that
no sé qué no sé qué Y le contesté en ese
moment is that he wants to fight such and such And I do
momento es que quiera pelear tal Y yo
n't know ask him ask him I mean
pues no sé pregúntale preguntale O sea
you look look if you want someone
tú Busca busca si quieres a alguien
look you won't find because in
busca no vas a encontrar porque es que a
four days in four days the
cuatro días a cuatro días la perra
veiled [ __ ] who is going to get into the ring I mean
velada quién se va a subir a un ring o
even if they tell you yes I told him go
sea aunque te digan que sí yo le dije va
and they're going to say yes and then they're going to go
y te van a decir que sí y luego van a ir
to their first training  They're going to try to
a su primer entrenamiento van a intentar
do a three-round sparring and they're
hacer un sparring de tres rounds y se
going to die because it's not possible in
van a morir porque no es posible a
four days It's not possible at least
cuatro días No es posible al menos de
what you've been doing and what you've been training for months, maybe
que llevas además de que lleves en meses
people for more if you
entrenando posible gente por más si tú
think you have condition I'm going to
crees que tienes condición te voy a
tell you one thing, one thing, get in there dude Get in there
decir una cosa una cosa métete un güey
sparring and you'll realize you do
Métete un sparring y te vas a dar cuenta
n't have it By the way, about Rivers,
que no tienes Por cierto sobre rivers
Goku made some pretty
Goku Hizo unos comentarios bastante
weird comments saying that he had fallen in love with
raritos afirmando que se había enamorado
her and people are talking like they've
de ella y la gente está hablando como
seen this a little strange, you've been
que esto lo han visto un poco raro
acting strange lately, okay, I'll
actúas en forma extraño últimamente vale
put the clip and put it in the
os pongo el clip y poner en la caja de
comment box regarding what you think.
comentario con respecto a lo que pensáis
I told her to her face, we went to the
yo se lo dije en la cara fuimos a la
party and she was there, I've never had anything
fiesta y ella estaba yo nunca había algo
like that, I've never had anything like that, She's
así Nunca había algo así Ella
quiet, little Sandy, little eyes,
tranquilita chiquita la Sandy ojitos
walks slowly, doesn't bother anyone,
camina Lento no molesta a nadie perfil
low profile, calm, it can't be, it can't be, the
bajo tranquila no puede ser no puede ser
ultimate woman is the
en la mujer definitiva es la mujer
ultimate woman, she's friends, it sounds kind of like SIM,
definitiva es amigos suena medio a SIM
but I'm in love with her, she really
pero estoy enamorado de ella de verdad
conquered me, she conquered me on another level and I
me conquistó me conquistó a otro nivel y
'm not talking about anything that
no estoy hablando de nada de lo que
you all think, I'm talking, I'm
ustedes piensa yo estoy hablando estoy
talking  I don't know for me she's a crack but she
hablando de no sé para mí es crack pero
was a crack but to
crack estaba pero para hacerle una
literally bow to her you can't do it I would
reverencia literal hacerle no se puede
never have been told that
Yo nunca a mí me llegaban a decir que
she was going to fight twice and I would never have
ella iba a pelear dos veces y nunca lo
believed it I didn't know anything
hubiera creído yo no sabía nada se puso
the coscu got romantic Sara vikin in her
romántico el coscu Sara vikin en su
live has been commenting again on
directo ha estado comentando otra vez
some things about the evening
alguna que otra cosilla sobre la velada
and she wanted to point out all those
y ha querido señalar a todas aquellas
people I don't know who she's referring to
personas no sé a quién se refiere en
specifically but I can think of a few
concreto pero se me ocurren unas cuantas
who are always pointing out
que siempre andan señalándoles de nazi a
her and auronplay as Nazis and then they have like a
ella y auronplay y luego tienen como
certain single thought me from here
cierto pensamiento único yo de aquí
Well on Twitter I've seen a lot
Bueno pues en Twitter he visto un montón
of people who got very intense
de gente no que se puso como muy intensa
against her and against auron
en contra de ella y en contra de auron
because she was the worst She wasn't the worst in the
porque era lo peor No era lo peor en el
world of streaming she was the elite that
mundo de los streaming era la élite que
had to be discovered and then you've
había que descubrir y luego te los has
seen them at the evening hanging out with the
visto en la velada arrejuntándose con
worst people and with people of the worst
gente de lo peor y con gente de la peor
caliber What a great fandom I have I love
calaña Qué gran fandom tengo me encanta
my fandom I can be more grateful in
mi fandom puedo estar más agradecida en
my fandom where they always defend me
mi fandom que me defienden siempre A
Tooth and nail she interrupts to comment
capa y espada interrumpe para comentar
that they've  nominate in a
que la han vuelto a nominar en un
contest that exists in the United States
concurso que hay en los Estados Unidos
for the 100 most beautiful people I don't know what
de las 100 personas más guapas no sé qué
contest it is But I hope she applies
concurso es Pero espero que se presente
and wins since I can't go they've
y lo gane ya que yo no puedo ir me han
nominated me again the second year in a row I don't
vuelto a nomina segundo año consecutivo
know why I don't know what the
no sé por qué no sé que tienen los
Americans have with me but they've nominated me again
americanos conmigo pero me han vuelto a
for one of the 100 most
nominar a una de las 100 caras más
beautiful faces in the world Thank you very much I
bonitas del mundo Muchísimas gracias
can only tell you from here for me
solo puedo decirle desde aquí para mí
that doesn't mean anything it's not going to change
eso sí no significa nada no va a cambiar
my life but double domination
mi vida pero doble dominación el año
last year and this year if you want to vote for me you
pasado y este año si me queréis votar
can do it I'm not forcing you or anything and
podéis hacerlo no os obligo ni mucho
much less if you have to pay
menos y mucho menos si tenéis que pagar
eh And then I continue Thanking her
eh Y luego continúo Agradeciendo a su
fandom for the support they always
fandom por el apoyo que siempre le
give her Although she says she caught
brinda Aunque dice haber pillado a
someone who she thought supported her
alguien que ella pensaba que la apoyaba
but apparently she discovered
pero que al parecer habría descubierto
that he has another account from which he
que tiene otra cuenta desde la que le
throws hate at her or something like that I don't know
tira hate o algo así por el estilo no sé
how you understand it I mean
cómo lo entendéis ustedes
in the end it's really funny to me that they
o sea al final me hace mucha gracia que
called us like me auron nazi Haha
nos llamaban como a mí auron nazi Jaja
But there are people who literally I mean
Pero es que hay gente que literal o sea
behave like a nazi what a roll  eh
se comporta como una nazi qué rollo eh
If you're not in favor of such and such you are that baba
Si no estás a favor de tal eres esa baba
you know what I'm telling you you know it's like that
sabéis lo que te digo sabes es como ese
being Nati friends
ser Nati amigos
then don't waste your time either, I mean
entonces tampoco perdáis el tiempo o sea
if they're doing a propaganda today that you
si están haciendo hoy una propaganda que
flip out, well let's see in the end you were born
flipas pues a ver al final lo naciste
beautiful you know what I'm telling you is that of course
bello sabéis lo que os digo es que claro
So nothing guys notice that not that
Entonces nada chicos notan que tampoco
much that I'm just very
tanto que yo simplemente estoy muy
proud of you eh I really think
orgullosa de vosotros eh De verdad creo
that in my community there are fake people also
que mi comunidad hay gente fake también
something has reached me today we'll find out
algo me ha llegado hoy lo averiguaremos
right girls and boys now now no no no
verdad chicas y chicos ahora ahora no no
I am a realohoro No yeah yeah yeah I'm not
no yo soy realojuro No ya ya ya ya no me
talking about people who have an account
refiero a gente que tiene una cuenta
Arroyo this support and then have another
Arroyo este apoyo y luego tiene otra
account where they dedicate themselves to insulting me and
cuenta donde se dedica a bardearme y
doing viral things out of context
hacer cosas virales fuera de contexto
Wow man I mean it's to take and
Guau tío o sea es que es para [__] y
hit a beast in the face to that
pegarle una bestia en toda la cara a esa
person but well anyway it's terrible
persona pero bueno en fin es terrible
well it remains to be corroborated eh terrible
bueno queda corroborarlo eh terrible
terrible no no yes yes yes
terrible no no
the worst thing is that I think I follow
sí sí sí lo peor es que creo que sigo
that person because I thought it was
esa persona rollo porque pensaba que era
my fandom you know but Wow I don't know that's
mi fandom sabes pero Wow No sé ese es
all very neither let's see at this point
todo muy tampoco a ver a estas alturas
in life nothing surprises me from anyone You
de la vida no me sorprende nada de nadie
know  what I say so it wouldn't
Sabes lo que digo así que tampoco me
surprise me too much on the other hand
sorprendería mucho por otro lado
regarding the issue of offers to
respecto al tema de ofertas de
participate in events and to meet with
participar en eventos y de juntarse con
people, some collaborations and so on, well
gente algunas colaboraciones y demás
she says that for the
pues ella dice que prefiere por el
moment she prefers to stay on her own, be
momento mantenerse a su rollo estar
calm with her community in Chile,
tranquilita con su comunidad de chile
just Solín alone and I think she should be
solo Solín solito y yo creo que tener
more careful about who she meets with than
más cuidadito de con quien se junta que
not, I always talk to my community and
no que siempre hablo con mi comunidad y
things end up being taken out of context, that's what
se acaban sacando cosas de contexto es
I don't like about jazz chatting,
lo que no me gusta de los jazz chatting
you know what I'm telling you, this is what I don't
sabéis lo que os digo esto es lo que no
like at all because in the end I spend
me gusta nada porque al final me tiro
two hours here talking to my
aquí dos horas hablando como con mi
community and you know the amount of
comunidad y ya sabéis la cantidad de
people obsessed with me who are every
gente obsesionada conmigo que está todos
day leaking my name and they
los días filtrando mi nombre y ya me
start to show me clips out of context
empiezan a sacar clips fuera de contexto
and development, you know, I don't like it. Apart from that, you
y desarrollo sabes no me Mola Aparte ya
see, I mean, I'm a person who goes
veis o sea yo soy una persona que va a
completely on her own, but I have been
su rollo completamente pero yo he estado
number one in viewers for two years,
dos años siendo la número uno en viewers
2 years in which I ended up practically
2 años en los cuales acabé prácticamente
crazy and decided not to appear
loca de la cabeza y decidí no aparecer
anywhere, not even in events, they
en ninguna parte ni eventos ni a mí me
offered me a ton of things, I rejected them, they
ofrecieron un montón de cosas la rechacé
even offered me to make documentaries
me ofrecieron incluso hacer documentales
to reject absolutely everything, I don't
para rechazar absolutamente todo no
want to do a single  book I don't want to do
quiero hacer ni un libro no quiero hacer
anything I just want to be here in Chile
nada Solo quiero estar aquí de chile
because I feel like it, I mean it's the only
porque me apetece o sea es la única
reason why I stream if I don't have
razón por la que hago Stream si no tengo
any kind of desire to do more
ningún tipo de ganas de hacer más
competitions nor do I want to go through
competiciones ni quiero volver a pasar
the two years that I spent previously
los dos años que he pasado anteriormente
that yeah okay a lot of glass and such But
que sí okay montón de vidrios Y tal Pero
I almost went crazy by the way
yo casi acabo loca de la cabeza por
people would have pointed out this
cierto la gente habría señalado este
tweet from Susana that would have
tweet de Susana que se habría
spoken out against the hate that
manifestado en contra del hate que le
Rivers was receiving which I
estuvo cayendo rivers que estoy
completely agree with her but
Completamente de acuerdo con ella pero
people would be pointing her out because she didn't
la gente la estaría señalando porque no
think of doing the same with Beijing yesterday we
pensó hacer lo mismo con Beijing ayer
were talking about the funa that was being
estuvimos hablando de la funa que le
done to Comanche on social media and
estaban haciendo a Comanche en redes y
the truth is that to this day it continues
la verdad es que a día de hoy continúa
almost with the same intensity I
casi con la misma intensidad yo creo
personally believe from what I've been
personalmente por lo que he estado
reading above that people have
leyendo por encima que la gente se le ha
completely gone crazy and we were
ido completamente la olla y estábamos
talking a couple of days ago
hablando hace un par de días
precisely about this type of bullying on the
precisamente de este tipo de bullying en
internet and I don't know why they have given Carte
internet y no sé por qué han dado Carta
Blanche what they have done or at what point it is
blanca ha hecho o en qué momento se
allowed I mean they are messing with
permite O sea que se están metiendo con
the physique in a brutal way they are
el físico de una manera brutal le están
saying very wild things I don't know
diciendo cosas muy bestias no conozco
Comanche very well I only follow
mucho a Comanche yo solamente me sigo
him on social media but no  I have had no
con el en redes pero no he tenido ningún
dealings with him other than the one we had in
Trato con él más que el que tuvimos en
Squid Games And some
Los juegos del calamar Y algún mensaje
private messages and not much because I got banned
privado y poca cosa porque me banearon
from Twitch and such and I think he wrote to me I
de Twitch y demás y creo que me escribió
don't know if he's a good person or a bad person
no sé si es buena gente o mala gente
but really it's that I'm reading
pero realmente es que estoy leyendo las
things that are very crazy on
cosas que son muy locas en redes
social media a
sociales ha salido precisamente una
news story came out that claims that Comanche apart
noticia que afirma que Comanche aparte
from having some kind of bipolarity that I do
de tener algún tipo de bipolaridad que
n't know if it's true or not would have had
no sé si será cierto o no habría tenido
some other suicide attempt So be
algún que otro intento de suicidio Así
careful today a clip went viral
que cuidadito hoy se hizo viral un clip
where he does a bit of a strange promotion
donde él hace una promoción un poco rara
the truth is I'm going to fool ourselves a bit strangely
la verdad Nos voy a engañar un poco rara
to promote English classes and
para promocionar clases de inglés y la
people are humiliating him for this too
gente lo Está humillando también por
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
today yes
hoy sí
One Blow your house as far as I know blog is
One Blow your house que yo sepa blog es
a category on these pages but
una categoría en estas páginas pero blog
House blog that would be a blog here at home I'm
House eso sería un blog aquí a domicilio
going to leave you okay
te voy a dejar okay
There are certain mistakes due to not knowing English
Hay ciertos errores por no saber inglés
that are very expensive mega more for example
que salen caros mega más por ejemplo que
yesterday he was joining the
ayer se estuvo uniendo a la funa de
Comanche funa laughing at Green
Comanche riéndole las gracias al Green
gereche today he posted a tweet
gereche hoy ha puesto un tweet sin
however asking for caution and asking
embargo pidiendo cautela y pidiendo
people to calm down and also some of
calma a la gente y también algunos de
his friends Like for example Dead or
sus amigos Como por ejemplo el Dead o
Pipe pum would have come out to launch a
Pipe pum habrían salido a lanzar un
message of support today I have received the
mensaje de apoyo hoy me ha llegado la
final sentence for the complaint that I
sentencia en firme por la denuncia que
filed against sebon, their friend Juan
le puse a sebon el amigo de ellos Juan
who threatened me bestially and
que me amenazó bestialmente y
violently calmly on
violentamente tranquilamente en redes
social networks both in public and in
sociales tanto en público como en
private. I mean, he sent me a tweet in
privado O sea me puso un tweet en
public and then in case it was not
público y luego por si no me había
clear to me that he wanted to attack me, he
quedado claro de que me quería agredir
confirmed it to me privately if one day I
me lo confirmó por privado si un día te
see you on the street I will step on your head you son
veo por la calle Te piso la cabeza hijo
of a [ __ ] I have desire for you a long time ago you
de [__] te tengo ganas de hace tiempo
dropped several pearls to Juanito
que soltaste varias perlitas a Juanito
in your videos I let it go I even
en tus vídeos lo dejé pasar llegué hasta
felt sorry when they harassed you for
sentir pena cuando te acosaron por lo de
your son in a video that I saw on refi but
tu hijo en un vídeo que vi de refi pero
I see that he is still the same [ __ ] as
veo que sigue siendo el mismo [__] de
always I would like to see how you would
siempre me gustaría ver cómo te
feel if a streamer without coming to the
sentirías si un streamer sin venir a
point and if it was the same with your wife I
cuento y si era lo mismo con tu mujer te
swear by my dead that one day we
juro por mis muertos que un día nos
will meet then don't say I did not
encontraremos luego no digas que no te
warn you to see the context of this for whoever has
avise a ver el contexto de esto para el
lost it It is that I sent a
que se le haya perdido Es que yo puse un
tweet when they were fooling around the
tweet cuando estaban de cachondeo el
bifeíto between  amuran and massi
bifeíto entre amuran y massi la novia de
yo Juan's girlfriend if the editor is putting
yo Juan si el editor se está poniendo
the photograph on screen here well
por aquí en pantalla la fotografía pues
you can see that it was not a sexual photo or
podéis ver que no era una foto sexual ni
anything like that it was not obscene it was not
nada por el estilo no era nada obsceno
insulting it was nothing In
no era nada insultante no era nada De
fact it was nothing that they would not have done
hecho no era nada que no Hubieran hecho
themselves because eBay itself
ellos mismos porque el propio eBay la
challenged the two of them to be
retó a las dos a que fueran
participants in evening 3 and
participantes de la velada 3 y se
fight and other content creators
pelearan y otros creadores de contenido
have also played the same joke in
también han gastado la misma broma de
fact it seems to me that yo Juan himself
hecho me suena a que el propio yo Juan
has laughed at this joke in public
se ha reído de esta broma en público
now I don't remember if it was on Stream or in
ahora no me acuerdo si en Stream o en
tweets or something like that okay or on
tweets o algo por el estilo vale o en
Twitter I don't remember but I know that several
Twitter no me acuerdo pero sé que varios
creators made the same joke but
creadores hicieron la misma broma pero
nothing happens with them okay what happens If
con ellos no pasa nada vale lo pasa Que
I do it, what a crime, not
si la hago yo tremendo crimen no la
mobility, which as it could not be
movilidad que como no podía ser de otro
otherwise, it was absurd to think otherwise,
modo que era absurdo pensar lo contrario
like many other things that have been
como otras muchas cosas que se han
committed and are in process, I
cometido en y están en procesos lo
reported it I reported it at the time
denuncié lo denuncié en su momento
we had the trial in the trial he
tuvimos el juicio en el juicio él lo
recognized it and basically apart from
reconoció y básicamente aparte de
recognizing it I don't know if I will show you the
reconocerlo no sé si os enseñaré el
video at some point whatever but
vídeo en algún momento lo que sea pero
apart  of recognizing it basically what he
aparte de reconocerlo básicamente lo que
did was claim that it was justified
hizo fue alegar que estaba justificado
that this behavior was
que este comportamiento estaba
justified because I made that tweet
justificado porque yo hice ese tuit
because I made a meme with the friend and
porque yo hice un meme con la amiga y
a porn actress and then also above
una actriz porno y luego también sobre
all the argument that
todo el argumento que intentaban
both he and his lawyer were trying to use was that
utilizar tanto él como su abogado era
I have a gossip channel
que yo tengo un canal de salseo por lo
therefore since I look for controversy well I
tanto como yo busco la polémica pues
have to put up with these things
estas cosas las tengo que aguantar
because I caused them no you cannot
porque yo las provocó no no puedes
commit crimes against people
cometer delitos en contra de la gente
Okay and I say this for this one who is already
Vale y lo digo por este que ya está
convicted and is sentenced definitively and I
condenado y está condenado en firme y le
say it for other people who will
digo por otra gente a la que les va a
come across that I have a
venir de camino que yo tenga un canal de
gossip channel and that it has substance that it has
salseo y que tenga chicha que tenga
controversy and that it looks for a little bit of a
polémica y que busque un poquito el
game unless I suddenly
jueguecito a no ser que de repente me
go crazy and bite your
vuelva loco y le muerda una pierna a tu
grandmother's leg it seems completely
abuela me parece completamente
unnecessary to behave as if
innecesario comportarnos como si
we were in a square in a manner
estuviéramos en una plazoleta de manera
at least civilized and this one the other
cuanto menos civilizada y este el otro
day was also at the evening 3 or the
día estuvo también en la velada 3 o sea
evening there basically the atmosphere
la velada allí básicamente el ambiente
of guests that there were I don't even know
de invitados que había no sé ni a
how many they sentenced there were per
cuántas condenan que había por metro
square meter The Movida that not only
cuadrado La Movida que no solamente
lost the trial already spoke  I communicated at the
perdió el juicio ya habló comuniqué en
time they sentenced him to 600 euros plus
su momento lo condenaron a 600 euros más
costs honestly for my taste It
las costas sinceramente para mi gusto
should have been at least
Tendría que haber sido por lo menos el
double for my taste because I think what
doble para mi gusto porque me parece una
these two messages say is outrageous
barbaridad lo que dicen estos dos
but well I didn't insist
mensajes pero bueno tampoco insistí
too much no the thing is that he even
mucho no la movida es que él encima
appealed, I mean he had the nerve to
recurrió o sea tuvo las narices de
appeal, he sent the messages he made them
recurrir mandó los mensajes los puso
public he acknowledged it in court and
públicamente lo reconoció en el juicio y
appealed again claiming that I
recurrió volviendo a legar que es que yo
make gossip videos and that
hago vídeos de salseo y que es que yo
when I won the sentence I put
cuando he ganado la sentencia he puesto
there Juan in the title of the video that I
ahí yo Juan en el título del vídeo que
made a video announcing that I
me he hecho vídeo anunciando que he
won the trial and that I put them
ganado el juicio y que he puesto ellos
Juan in the title let's see the only thing missing was that
Juan en el título a ver solo faltaba
I have to ask
solo faltaba que yo tenga que pedir
permission to inform people of the
permiso para informar a la gente de las
consequences that you have if you commit
consecuencias que tienes si cometes
crimes against me the only thing missing was no I
delitos en contra mía solo faltaba no O
mean people commit crimes publicly
sea la gente comete delito públicamente
against me and the only thing missing was
contra mí y solo faltaba solo faltaba
that I in my media could not get the
que yo en mi medio no pudiera sacar la
information out and that I am a gossip channel
información y que soy un canal de salseo
that well tomorrow we will read more about
que bueno ya mañana nos leeré más exten
the sentence that is already final and cannot be
la sentencia que ya es firme ya no se
appealed okay he is sentenced
puede recurrir vale está condenado en
final I do not know  if I will put the video I don't
firme no sé si os pondré el vídeo No
think it's necessary
creo que haga falta tampoco es muy
this is not very relevant nor is there much
relevante esto no ni tiene mucha
discussion I think it has been made clear
discusión yo creo que ha quedado Claro
but basically the judge tells him that it does not
pero básicamente la jueza le dice que da
matter the way I have to grow
igual la manera que yo tenga de crecer
the content that I do that you
el contenido que yo haga que esto no lo
cannot do this okay This is not from
puedes hacer vale Esto no es de personas
civilized people that by the way
civilizadas que por cierto este caso me
Pablo Franco has won this case he has already
lo ha ganado Pablo Franco ya me ha
taken me to other cases and has another one on the
llevado a otros casos y tiene otro en
way I will surely stop by his channel
caminos Seguramente me pase por su canal
Or he by mine to comment on the
O él por el mío para comentar la
sentence yeri mua it turns out that he does
sentencia yeri mua que resulta que hace
live broadcasts every day on his
directos todos los días en su página de
Facebook page Also from what I've been
Facebook Además por lo que he estado
seeing he has a lot of impact on
viendo pues tiene mucha repercusión en
Facebook when he is talking about his
Facebook cuando está hablando de sus
controversies he usually gets around 50-60,000
polémicas suele rondar los 50-60.000
viewers he has had certain problems
espectadores ha tenido ciertos problemas
with the page there are many people who talk
con la página hay mucha gente que habla
about that Facebook gives a lot of problems with
de que Facebook da muchos problemas con
the page issue and that they have given him
el tema de la página y que le han metido
five strikes that he is about to lose
cinco strike que está a punto de perder
his account therefore and that he does not
su cuenta por lo tanto y que no sabe
even know that the
incluso que se estaría barajando la
possibility of taking her and eliminating
posibilidad de [__] ella y eliminarla a
her so as not to live with it being taken away I
ella para no vivir que se la quitan no
cannot argue anything against that logic
puedo argumentar nada ante esa lógica al
apparently Facebook to  through her
parecer Facebook a través de sus
followers they have discovered this girl
seguidores han descubierto a esta chica
and it seems that they had not located her
y Parece ser que no la tenían localizada
as one of the
como una de las creadoras de contenido
most relevant content creators within their platform
más relevante dentro de su plataforma
so they would have contacted
por lo que se habrían puesto en contacto
her when they have found out about all
con ella cuando se han enterado de toda
this movement and have agreed to meet with
esta movida y han acordado reunirse con
her to reach a solution and
ella para llegar a una solución e
try to remove the strikes And that she continues
intentar quitarle los strikes Y que siga
on the platform Good morning
en la plataforma Buenos días
well today I have a meeting
bueno el día de hoy tengo una reunión
with Facebook a meeting with me
con Facebook una reunión con me
and I don't know very well what it's going to be about Or
y no sé muy bien de qué va a tratar Ni
how long it's going to last but I'm excited I do
cuánto va a durar pero estoy emocionada
n't know if they're going to tell me you know
No sé igual si me van a decir sabes que
Jerry You're fired Thank you for all
Jerry Estás despedida Gracias por todo
your time working at Facebook
tu tiempo que has trabajado en Facebook
or if maybe they're going to help me
o si a lo mejor me van a ayudar a
solve some problems I have
resolver algunas problemáticas que tengo
with Facebook about policies and things well we
con Facebook de políticas y cosas pues
are here in the offices of meta
ya estamos aquí en las oficinas de meta
three four weeks I don't know there were five
tres cuatro semanas no sé fueron cinco
videos that committed a strike ok
videos que cometieron un strike ok
and we all know what happens when you put together a
y todas sabemos qué pasa cuando juntas
lot of strikes I am not demonetized they did not
muchos strikes no estoy desmonetizada no
take away my monetization I am at
me quitaron mi monetización estoy en
risk of losing the page this one they
riesgo de perder la página esta le
took away all the visibility all
quitaron toda la visibilidad toda Pasa
This happens and I didn't see how there would be
este y no veía como manera de que
a solution for my page I thought about
hubiera una solución a mi página pensé
deleting it myself well  my
eliminarla yo misma pues ya ser mi
last live and delete my page and I
último en vivo y eliminar mi página y yo
'm horrible and they didn't
es una horrible y eso que no me la
demonetize it just now at risk of
desmonetizaron solo ahorita en riesgo de
being deleted I said Well then I better do
ser eliminada dije Bueno pues mejor hago
one last live and delete it than I
un último en vivo y le elimino yo a que
deleted Facebook better I delete it myself
me eliminé Facebook mejor lo elimino yo
just keep my Instagram and already I mean
solo quedarme con mi Instagram y ya o
my audience is people who
sea mi audiencia es de gente que me
follow me and I have created a very
sigue y que he creado una comunidad muy
large and very strong community of live broadcasts
grande y muy fuerte de transmisiones en
and that at this moment I continue to be
vivo y que en este momento sigo siendo
the strongest Facebook streamer, I
la más fuerte en streamer de Facebook o
mean in Facebook streaming I am the
sea en streaming de Facebook Soy la más
strongest in Latin America and well it had seemed
fuerte de latinoamérica y pues se les
strange to them that they
había hecho raro que no
were not in that blog that they
estuvieran en esa bitácora que no
were not contemplated that this that the
estuvieran contemplada que esto que el
other but at the same time they
otro pero al mismo tiempo se dieron
realized that yes I am a very
cuenta que si estoy un streamer muy
strong and very big streamer but well I have my
fuerte y muy grande pero pues tengo mi
page in [ __ ] that's why they called me
página hecha [__] por eso me llamaron
because they want to help me because they want to help me
porque me querían porque me quieren
because they want to
ayudar porque me quieren ayudar porque
help me with what is happening
quieren ayudarme con lo que está pasando
my page and well I don't know I felt a lot of
mi página y pues no sé Sentí mucho
feelings I felt a lot of feelings
sentimientos sentí muchos sentimientos
Because because I didn't ask for help I
Porque porque yo no pedí ayuda yo ya
was already decided I mean there to delete
estaba decidida ya o sea allá eliminar
my page and I felt nice that the
mi página y Sentí bonito que que la
same platform in which I work
misma plataforma en la que trabajo me
offered me her help and nobody knew about this
ofreció su ayuda y nadie sabía de esto
nobody knew And I feel beautiful I feel very
nadie sabía Y siento bonito siento muy
beautiful and well every time I'm going to
bonito y pues ya cada vez voy a ir
grow more every time I'm becoming
creciendo más cada vez me voy haciendo
more adult Every time I'm going to become
más adulta Cada vez me voy a ir haciendo
more mature Maybe it comes slowly it comes
más madura A lo mejor llega lento llega
slowly I
lento
promise you dude I mean it's like what I
se los prometo güey o sea es como lo que
lived with my last partner I mean I feel like
viví con mi última pareja o sea siento
a lot of bad things happened very
que pasaron muchas cosas malas pero muy
bad things I mean things like dude that the
malas o sea cosas así de que güey que la
house he and what a [ __ ] dude I mean things that
casa él y que [__] güey O sea cosas que
you say but I say I had to live it I mean I
tú dices pero yo digo lo tenía que vivir
told them do you remember when I
o sea yo les dije se acuerda cuando yo
told you once
les dije alguna vez
Let me have the boyfriend I want that I have to
Déjenme tener el novio que yo quiera que
live what I have to
yo tengo que vivir lo que tengo que
live there it is I told them let me live
vivir ahí está yo les dije déjeme vivir
and make mistakes the way I want okay There it
y equivocarme como yo quiero okay Ahí
is there is what I told you that I had to live
está ahí está lo que les dije que tenía
and I had to make mistakes lived
que vivir y tenía que equivocar vivido
the girl is a streamer they keep complaining
la chica es streamer se siguen quejando
that there are people who cut and crop
de que haya gente que corte y recorte
certain shots of their live streams to
ciertas tomas de sus directos para
sexualize them without consent I
sexualizarlas sin consentimiento yo
think two things about this okay On the one
sobre esto pienso dos cosas vale Por una
hand I think there are girls I don't know if it's the
parte creo que hay chicas no sé si es el
case with Jona or Avi because I don't watch their live
caso de Jona o de Avi porque no veo sus
streams  Avi for example yes I have
directos a Avi por ejemplo sí que le he
seen her upload photos maybe her life of
visto subir fotos a lo mejor su vida de
tones or whatever showing her body
tonos o lo que sea enseñando su cuerpo
I think even in a thong, not Luna
creo que incluso en tanga no a Luna
Clark who I don't know much I have followed
Clark que la conozco poco me he seguido
her recently on social media the truth is
con ella hace poco en redes la verdad es
that I don't know okay I mean I don't know if she
que lo desconozco vale o sea no sé si lo
does it or not the truth is I don't know
hace o no lo hace la verdad no lo sé
but I know that there are girls who
pero sé que hay chicas que ellas mismas
sexualize themselves okay I know that there are girls who
se sexualizan vale sé que hay chicas que
lend themselves and make that
ellas mismas se prestan y hace ese
content on purpose which I insist I don't know
contenido a propósito que insisto no sé
if it's the case with those two in the
si es el caso de ellas dos en los
live shows okay but apparently well
directos vale pero por lo visto bueno
This is something that has existed
Esto es una cosa que ha existido de toda
forever no apparently the birds
la vida no al parecer los pajarillos
look for the clips Maybe she gets
pues buscan los clips A lo mejor que se
up from the chair, turns around, you can
levanta de la silla que se da la vuelta
see her shorts no that her
que se le ve el pantaloncillo no que que
pants are tight, her bra
tiene el pantalón ajustado el sujetador
whatever Okay and they upload those clicks as
lo que sea Vale y suben esos clics como
erotic content I mean it's a little
contenido erótico o sea da un poquito de
strange no because there are pages on the internet
cosa no porque hay páginas en internet
where you can find this type of
donde puedes encontrar este tipo de
content and you don't have to be so
contenido y no hace falta que esté tan
sick to start doing this I've
enfermo de ponerte a hacer esto Yo he
found everything from the streamers okay
encontrado de todo de las streamer vale
for example on YouTube they appear
por ejemplo en YouTube te aparecen
recommended  I'm sure you thought
recomendados seguro que os ha parecido
Cristinini's shorts were just a bunch
el short de cristinini en fin un montón
of nonsense like that, no Cristinini gets up
de movidas así no cristinini se levanta
from her chair
de la Silla
Well here you have the tweets having to
Pues aquí tenéis los tweets tener que
fight against the wanker forums
luchar contra los foros de pajeros
sharing our photos and
compartiendo nuestras fotos y
telling us saved accounts summarizing
diciéndonos guardadas cuentas resumiendo
sexualized clips nude made with
clips sexualizados nude hecho con
Artificial Intelligence unsolicited dick pics
Inteligencia artificial fotos de pollas
with tributes and the
no solicitadas con tributes y la lista
endless list of all this [ __ ] that we
interminable de todas estas [__] que
put up with day after day and Luna answers the
aguantamos día tras día y contesta Luna
best thing is to then go to the
lo mejor es que luego ir a la guardia
civil guard to report the fake nudes and have them
civil a denunciar los nudes falsos y que
tell you that since you are dedicated to
te digan que como te dedicas a redes
social networks That's good because it makes you
sociales Eso es bueno porque así te hace
more famous my goodness How crazy How
más famosa madre mía Qué locura Qué
crazy let's see that
locura a ver entiendo que no ha ganado
the civil guard has not won because they are not going to
la guardia civil porque no se van a
investigate to see who it was
poner a investigar a ver quién ha sido
nor do I think there are ways and so on okay
ni creo que haya formas y demás vale
But if they have answered this it is
Pero si le han contestado esto es
quite crazy no on the other hand Luna
bastante loco no por otro lado luna
has also come out to deny a move
también ha salido a desmentir una movida
And the fact is that they have been speculating about having
Y es que han estado especulando con
seen her flirting with a
haberla visto tonteando con un jugador
soccer player in the VIP area of ​​the evening
de fútbol en la zona VIP de la velada lo
which apparently is a lie and The
cual por lo visto pues es mentira y La
girl says that  he doesn't even know the
chica dice que ni siquiera conoce al
footballer a certain Federico Valverde who
futbolista un tal Federico Valverde
starts for Real Madrid here I will be
titular el Real Madrid aquí os estaré
showing you the thread that he
poniendo en pantalla el hilo que ha
made the truth is that the thread is
hecho la verdad que el hilo es
very long if you want to stop it
larguísimo si ustedes queréis pararlo
then you can stop it and read it but
pues podéis pararlo y leerlo pero
basically it says that he doesn't
básicamente viene a decir que no lo
know him You're welcome and that he was there that if he
conoce De nada y que estaba allí que si
had them next to him well what bad
los tenía al lado pues pues Que mala
luck that they were there No I have been
suerte que ahí estaban No ya os estuve
commenting to you many times I don't know if here
comentando muchas veces no sé si aquí
but the live ones I'm sure that
pero los directos Estoy seguro que una
once the evening is over suddenly you are
vez que terminase la velada de repente
going to see how magically a
Vais a ver mágicamente cómo aparece un
lot of these streamers appear not only
montón de estos streamers no solamente
those who have participated but also those
los que han participado sino también los
who have accepted the invitation and have gone
que han aceptado la invitación y han ido
to the VIP area they have taken photos in the
a la zona Vips han hecho fotitos en el
photocall suddenly finding out
fotocol de repente enterándose
finding out how serious it is that they
enterándose de lo grave que es que hayan
put coscu in there getting very indignant
metido a coscu ahí indignándose mucho
basically okay suddenly now that
básicamente vale de repente ahora que ha
the evening is over You are going to start seeing in
pasado la velada Vais a empezar a ver en
the next few days a lot of these
los siguientes días a un montón de estos
creators finding out that you recorded this
creadores enterándose de que grabes esto
and unfollowing coscu and complaining
y dejando de seguir a coscu y quejándose
device you are going to see it not for now
device ya lo Vais a ver no de momento
today what has happened  people say is
hoy lo que se ha dado cuenta la gente es
that Germán Garmendia has stopped following
que Germán Garmendia ha dejado de seguir
Coco on social media Goku is still
a Coco en redes sociales Goku sigue
keeping the [ __ ] up Germán but Germán
manteniendo el follo Germán pero Germán
to him there wouldn't be many people pointing out the
a él no habría mucha gente señalando el
fact that in the last few hours Germán
hecho de que las últimas horas Germán
uploaded some stories with María Becerra and it
subió unas historias con María Becerra y
seems that they would have been
es que por lo visto habrían estado
together Chatting before leaving Spain
juntos Charlando antes de irse de España
It's likely that the two of them when they got
Es probable que los dos cuando se han
together remember that María Becerra had
juntado recordar que María Becerra Tuvo
a controversy with Goku the same day before
una polémica con Goku el mismo día antes
the evening that they started
de la velada que se hayan puesto a
chatting that they made him green or
charlar que lo hayan puesto verde o lo
whatever and that Germán Well now Dallas did
que sea y que Germán Pues ahora Dallas
n't convince him but now for the moment
no lo convenció pero ahora de momento
María Becerra Well yes there are also many
María Becerra Pues sí también hay mucha
people who speculate that it could have
gente que especula que podría haber
happened that Germán would have been upset by
ocurrido que a Germán le hubiera sentado
that click that there is not of the That
mal aquello clic que hay no de la Que
Coco formed and the lack of respect even
formó Coco y la falta de respeto incluso
mockery towards Germán after having
burlas hacia Germán después de haberle
won the fight we will see if
ganado el combate ya veremos a ver si
the Chilean did something publicly or not
hice algo públicamente el chileno o no
by the way, a news that has caught my
por cierto una noticia que me ha llamado
attention and that you have
mucho la atención y que me lo habéis
sent me quite a bit is the fact that they have
mandado bastante es el hecho de que han
discovered that Gonzavela was in the
descubierto que gonzavela estuvo en la
VIP area of ​​the  evening but she wasn't
zona VIP de la velada pero no estaba
invited by ibai or anyone from the
invitada por ibai ni por nadie de la
organization it's something that catches my
organización es algo que me llama la
attention with everything that crowded
atención con todo lo que apeloteado a
the whole group
todo el grupito
massages chocas well she got
masajea al chocas bueno conmigo se
angry with me because I criticized chocan no
enfadó porque critiqué al chocan no sin
however I haven't seen her criticize choca
embargo no la he visto criticar al choca
for the trick or for Katy or
por lo del trucazo ni por lo de Katy ni
anything like that come on this girl
nada por el estilo vamos esta chica me
dedicated a series of live shows to me and she's
dedicó una serie de directos y la tiene
really mad at me she's got my
súper tomada conmigo me tiene hecha la
back because I criticized choca when he
cruz porque critiqué al choca cuando se
messed with the people who donated the
metió con la gente que le donaban los
live shows to him okay I think it was something like that no Well it
directos vale creo que era algo así no
turns out that this girl being
Pues resulta ser que esta chica siendo
so close to gemita and the whole gang had to be
tan cercana a gemita y a toda la tropa
invited the coconut the coscu was the one who
la tuvo que invitar el coco el coscu fue
invited her to the evening I
el que la invitó a la velada tengo
really want to say it I only had one
muchas ganas de decirlo tuve solo una
person invited to the evening which made me
persona invitada a la velada que me dio
impotent that she wasn't invited a
impotencia que no esté invitada una
girl from Spain that I've known for like
chica de España que yo conozco hace como
five years obviously only from the scene let's
cinco años obviamente solo de la escena
say that it goes through my cousins ​​I go
digamos de que pasa por mis primos paso
through her Stream and the best thing so that they don't
por su Stream y la mejor para que no
start breaking the ball the girl
empiecen a romper la pelota la chica
has a boyfriend and he's the boyfriend  I know him
tiene novio y es el novio se lo conozco
and I take excellent
y me llevo excelente
detention I felt sorry that
detenido me dio pena que esté como tan
the scene here is so cracked I put myself in
agrietada la escena acá yo me pongo en
the place of the Awards and I know that there are
el lugar de los Awards y yo sé que hay
people with whom I may not have a
gente con la que quizás no tengo
relationship but they are from the scene and I feel
relación pero es de la escena y siento
that we have to invite her we were in a
que Hay que invitarla estábamos en un
stadium for 65,000 people how is there not going to be
estadio para 65.000 personas como no va
room for a streamer who is
a haber lugar para una streamer que es
known from the environment that I knew that you
conocida del ambiente que conocía que
know that they are going to ask for photos and that you
sabés que le van a pedir fotos y que
know that people are going to be
sabes que la gente se va a poner
happy to see her and that you know that she has been
contento de verla y que sabes que ha
to a lot of events and it is not
estado en un montón de eventos y no es
about criticizing ibai it is not about criticizing
por criticar a ibai no es por criticar a
anyone because her head is in 50
nadie porque tiene la cabeza en 50
places at once and she cannot ask for a
lugares a la vez y no puede pedir una
separate ticket because I did not have
entrada aparte porque yo no tenía
tickets or more than my team obviously and I
entradas o sea más que mi equipo obvio y
invited gonza gonza is gonzavela a
invité a gonza gonza es gonzavela un
streamer from here in Spain who has been irrele for a long time
streamer de acá de España que hace mucho
now does asmr I hate asmr
irrele ahora hace asmr yo odio el asmr
So I do not watch Stream more But do not
Así que no veo más Stream Pero eso no se
take that the wrong way the thing is that she
lo tome mal la cuestión es que yo ella
told me hey I hope you do well I do not
me dijo hey espero que te vaya bien no
know what and I told her that you are not coming  talking you
sé qué y le dije que no venís hablando
saw her tells me no it's that they haven't
viste me dice no es que no me han
invited me and I couldn't believe it or rather I
invitado y yo no podía creer o sea no
couldn't believe it Since no one from production
podía creer Como nadie de producción
said Hey, this girl is a girl let's
decía Che esta esta chica es una chica
say known regardless of whether she's a
digamos conocida independientemente que
boy or a girl but she's a girl
sea chico o chica pero es una chica
known in the environment How come she's not
conocida del ambiente Cómo cómo no está
invited or rather What can a
invitada o sea en Qué te puede cambiar
person change you Tell her that yes she was like yes she
una persona Díganle que sí estuvo como
was
que sí estuvo
obviously there yes I invited her I
obvio que estuvo si Yo la invité
got the ticket I spoke to Carmen who
conseguí la entrada hablé con Carmen que
sends her greetings and I told her I have a
le mando un saludo y le dije tengo un
streamer friend that I would love to
streamer amiga que me encantaría poder
invite If it's not a bother and she said yes
invitar Si no es molestia y me dijo sí
of course Give me the name and she gives her
por supuesto Pásame el nombre y le pasa
the name and she was obviously I know
el nombre y ella fue obviamente yo sé
that this is going to generate the typical the
que esto va a generar el típico la
typical [ __ ] of all that because I know
típica boludez de todo eso porque yo sé
how my people are but I don't give a damn I'm
cómo es mi gente pero me chupo un huevo
not going to avoid saying it just because
no voy a evitar decirlo solo porque
you guys draw conclusions the first
ustedes saquen conclusiones los primeros
confirmed participants of the next
participantes confirmados del próximo de
challenge in ark have been Willy and Vegeta
desafío en ark han sido Willy y Vegeta
the event will take place on July 12 and
el evento se realizará el 12 de julio y
at the moment apart from them being the
de momento aparte de ser ellos dos los
first confirmed they have also
primeros confirmados también se han
confirmed that It's logical it was
confirmado el propio de que Es lógico se
expected it's not a surprise and
esperaba no es ninguna sorpresa y
nefarious Ricky is being  canceled on
nefarius Ricky está siendo cancelado en
social media for this tweet that you
las redes sociales por este tweet que
're seeing below I know
estáis viendo a continuación yo conozco
this place I've been there It's also the
este lugar he estado allí También es el
Warner Park in Madrid which by the way I did
parque Warner de Madrid que por cierto
n't like much the last time I went it's been a
no me gustó mucho la última vez que fui
while since I went I don't know if it will have
ya hace tiempo que no voy no sé si habrá
improved if I go again I'll tell you but
mejorado si vuelvo a ir os comento pero
basically Well it's a tw it's supposed to be
básicamente Bueno es un tw se supone que
sexist and blah blah blah Ricky puts
es machista y bla bla bla Ricky pone
this type of content on many
este tipo de contenido en muchas
occasions precisely to stir up the
ocasiones precisamente para mover el
hornets' nest very well Ricky I like that and
avispero muy bien Ricky me gusta eso y
Ricky's girlfriend has come out to
la novia de Ricky pues ha salido a
defend them saying that it was
defenderlos diciendo que la idea fue de
her idea so people have been made to look
ella así que la gente ha quedado en
ridiculous not basically the people who have
ridículo no básicamente la gente que ha
criticized this well hacked as
criticado esto pues hackeado como
always Spring today participated in
siempre Spring hoy ha participado en el
club 113 which you already know is the podcast and
club 113 que ya sabe que es el podcast y
talked about several topics for example
habló de varios temas por ejemplo de
Kick which apparently Spring would also
Kick que al parecer Spring También
be flirting with this platform
estaría coqueteando con esta plataforma
listening to the offers that they are
escuchando las ofertas que le están
offering him and at the moment even if
ofreciendo y de momento aunque no cuaje
nothing comes to fruition it seems that he has
nada pues parece ser que tiene abierta
the possibility of listening to these offers
la posibilidad de escuchar estas ofertas
he says that at the moment he has nothing Clear
dice Que de momento no tiene nada Claro
nor has anything decided but that he does
ni tiene nada decidido pero que sí que
think that Twitch should think more about
piensa que Twitch debería pensar más en
its creators What a coincidence that
sus creadores Qué casualidad que todo el
everyone when  have you found out that
mundo cuando se ha enterado que ha
this platform has appeared that is
aparecido esta plataforma que está
offering so much money all of a sudden? Are you
ofreciendo tanta pasta de repente pues
complaining about Twitch's treatment? Have you
Se está quejando del trato de Twitch no
complained about Twitch's treatment on
se han quejado del trato de Twitch en
many other occasions that it
muchas otras ocasiones que sí que
was really worth staying? Like for
realmente era para quedarse Como por
example the blacklist of
ejemplo la lista Negra de los juegos del
squid games, censorship, percentages, well,
calamar la censura los porcentajes en
a lot of things, no, the issue of
fin un montón de movidas no el tema de
strikes, bans, a lot of
los strikes los baneos un montón de
things? No, but well, basically that's why it
cosas No pero bueno básicamente para eso
's good that there is competition, not
es bueno que exista la competencia no
so that the other platform gets its act together
para que la otra plataforma se ponga la
and so that you can pull
pila y para que tú puedas tirar un
the rope a little bit. Have you had an offer
poquito de la cuerda has tenido oferta
from Kick? Yes,
de Kick sí
something catches your attention, nothing catches my
te llama la atención algo nada me llama
attention, the platform
la atención la plataforma
[Laughs]
[Risas]
at some point, I mean, I really have a
algún momento o sea realmente tengo
contract with Twitch. But obviously
contrato con Twitch Pero obviamente
I also listen, I like to listen,
escucho a mí me gusta escuchar
but I look, of course, no, but
pero miro claro no pero es muy muy
everything that platform offers is very, very tempting,
tentador todo lo que te ofrece esa
but at the same time it's not safe, I mean, it does
plataforma pero a la vez no es seguro o
n't generate that much security for me,
sea a mí no me genera tanta seguridad
but there's that thing that it's good,
pero está eso de que de que está bueno
maybe it's good. And also those moments,
igual está bueno Y también esos momentos
moments in which you either take advantage of it and it
momentos con los cuales o aprovechás y
goes well, or you take advantage of it and it goes wrong, but
sale bien o aprovechás y sales mal pero
within all those moments, too, of
dentro de todos esos momentos también
course, but also I  I'm seeing that
claro pero también yo estoy viendo que
a lot of people who leave are allowed to continue.
mucha gente que se va les dejan seguir
I'm looking at Twitch, yes, that's a
estoy mirando en Twitch sí que eso es un
totally senior Game. I mean, you don't have to say
Game senior total O sea no tienes que
goodbye. Because everything that had
despedirte Porque todo lo que había
happened, I would like to read the fine print. I
pasado me gustaría leer la letra pequeña
suppose that what they're doing
Supongo que o sea lo que están haciendo
is precisely that you can learn on
es justamente que puedas aprender en
Twitch in order to move the audience, it
Twitch para ir trasladando el público
completely breaks with the
rompe completamente con la plataforma
previous platform. Okay, deflate and come here
anterior Vale desinflate y vente aquí
deflated, I don't know
desinflado no le
[Laughs]
[Risas]
but Amazon, I mean, Amazon doesn't see Twitch
pero Amazon o sea Amazon no ve Twitch
as it doesn't invest as much in them, it sees it
como no invierte tanto en ellos lo ve
as a loss. Amazon to Twitch, I notice that
como perdida Amazon a Twitch yo noto eso
with the changes they usually make. I notice
con los cambios que suelen hacer yo noto
that Amazon,
que Amazon
up there,
arriba
really handles Twitch very well on
realmente Twitch se maneja muy bien en
some occasions and very badly on others. I
algunas ocasiones y muy mal en otras yo
mean, when I went to Twitch, I met a lot of
o sea cuando fui a Twitch conocí muchos
Twitch staff and it's very cool, they
staff de Twitch y muy buena onda te
tell you the changes they're going to make, they
dicen los cambios que van a hacer te
keep you very much on the sidelines, but out of nowhere they take
mantienen muy al margen pero de la nada
away the 3% of the thing, that they
te sacan lo del 3% de coso eso que lo
canceled later and nobody was
cancelaron después y Nadie estaba
aware of. I mean, almost always, everything
enterado O sea casi siempre todo lo
new they were implementing, they didn't
nuevo que iban implementando no lo iban
tell us about it and then they came out with that
diciendo nosotros y después sacaron esa
regulation that was very controversial, no,
normativa que era muy polémica no
we didn't know anything and I'm
nosotros no sabíamos nada y yo estoy
hired by Twitch but nothing  I mean, I
contratado por Twitch pero nada o sea yo
feel like Twitch needs to give a
siento que Twitch tiene que darle un
little more attention to the creators because they
poco más de caso a los creadores porque
also, I mean, they themselves always
también o sea ellos mismos siempre lo
say it without the creators there is no Twitch
dicen sin los creadores no existe Twitch
and nothing family, here we are leaving
y nada familia por aquí vamos dejando el
today's video I hope
videito de hoy Espero que haya sido de
you liked it I send you a huge hug
vuestro agrado os mando un abrazo enorme
Congratulations to whoever got the
Enhorabuena al que le haya tocado el
video game here on screen I
videojuego por aquí en pantalla te
will be showing you how to redeem it Remember
estaré poniendo como canjearlo Recuerda
that I am here more or less every
que estoy aquí más o menos todos los
day at the same time more or less okay And
días a la misma hora más o menos vale Y
if you like it and are interested in this type
que si te gusta y te interesa este tipo
of content Show me with your like
de contenido Demuéstramelo con tu like
share it subscribe and I am
compártelo suscríbete y me interesa
very interested in your opinion on all the
muchísimo vuestra opinión de todos los
topics in the comments box So I will
temas en la caja de comentarios Así que
be reading you family A huge kiss I'm leaving
os estaré leyendo familia Un beso enorme
goodbye go [ __ ] yourself
me voy adiós que os den
[Music]
[Música]